hello it's your favorite sports DK here
don't forget to hit that subscribe
button to join the fastest growing
community on YouTube Remember night cap
doesn't happen without you so please
subscribe or you're going to make oo
cry Lord day said uh Amanda was on your
ass in that interview did y'all see the
interview with Amanda seals I I missed
it I missed it I keep seeing I keep
seeing all the tweets and all all the
tweets are the same I can't believe I
agree with Amanda seals so
does everyone not like Amanda seal or
something I I don't know the backstory
but for some reason whatever she said it
must have been good because everybody
agrees with her whatever it mean yeah
she was
uh Hollywood especially black Hollywood
is kind of shunder and uh you know
everybody is kind of
shaped through their childhood and their
personal experience so you see things
you see life through your prism your l l
right right right and so she's had some
things in her life that kind
of makes her Ultra defensive she's a
she's a highly intelligent woman very
intelligent very well
read
but I think sometimes you know she
thinks everybody's out get her and so
until until she's comfortable with you
she's gonna keep that guard up she GNA
keep the guard up because I asked her
for a hug earlier she like like Noah I
don't hug I asked I said give me some DB
she ain't want to give me no DB but once
I told her I said Amanda this is a safe
space you can tell your story right she
saw it back she paused she like can I
have a
hug and then she was
cool I think a lot of things
that and people like I was trying to
invalidate her experience no I wasn't
it's the same thing I told Mo'Nique when
Mo'Nique said
I try you know I was trying to get this
role and Oprah told me to go blah blah
blah for right and she ended up getting
the rooll I said well Monique did you
ever think that they were looking for a
black heavy set woman and there were you
two are probably the only two in
Hollywood and she said oh okay that
makes sense and so when she said the
white lady had uh her teacher I said
Amanda did it ever cross your mind
that I don't know where you from but
where I grew up o
kids never corrected a parent or an
adult corrected yes it and that's what I
said I said I said Amanda did you think
maybe because you were a child even
though you were right the mere fact that
a child corrected an adult now maybe in
today's time that's fine maybe where in
some places you grew up but I don't ever
remember being around being in a
situation A Child couldn't even
interrupt an adult conversation you
couldn't p on your parents or your
grandparents leg and say hey hey hey hey
hey I'm like huh no so that's what I was
saying I said maybe maybe Amanda it
wasn't racism maybe it was the fact that
a child was correcting an
adult but that was her experience that's
what that's what and like I said I mean
that's how she felt about it but I enjoy
the interview I enjoy talking to people
yeah I mean everybody and I try
not I do my research but I try to go in
as with as clean a slate as I possibly
can because I don't want what someone
else has said about her to influence
what I think of her right yeah I'm gonna
come up I'm gonna ask the questions and
then at the end of the day hopefully she
when she sees it she'll be pleased with
the finished product but I ain't got no
problem with Manda seals she was great
uh she's very funny she has uh and I do
believe some of the people have done her
wrong and I think a lot of a lot of
because that's what you deal with we all
go through it dealing with men or women
you're not dating them you're dating
their childhood their past traumas
that's what you that's what you got to
get past so I'm excited I was excited to
have her uh she was great she taught me
a lot of things uh but she oh she's
highly highly highly Highly Educated
she's real versed she can sing she's a
comedian she's a
writer is is she she married no she's
not married she's not married the same
day I mean yes I'm I'm I'm listening to
you list all the qualities that she has
and I'm just curious if if she was
married because that that I mean that
sounds like that that's a great cat for
someone yeah yeah yeah no that sounds
like some flaws for some
because as educated as she is right yeah
she's there's a standard of a man that
she's looking for right yeah if it's not
on the same educational level as her
she's gonna right down on and with that
is if they're more educated than
her then they talking down to her these
are the type of women that will
typically be single because they can't
find equal partner to yeah they are she
she wants someone that that's that's
versed she wants someone that's
inquisitive she wants someone that wants
to travel I mean look to each his own oo
I'm not everybody's cup of tea I
understand that right Gil's not
everybody's cup of tea even with the
kind of money even with the kind of
finances you found your mate ra right
even with gills and our finance we
understand that some people like I I I
don't care how much he can have a
billion dollars I ain't rocking with him
and that's okay right I can have a
different perspective than Amanda that's
okay I don't think any less of her I
don't think any more of myself but
people like well just because I didn't
agree with everything she said oh you
trying to invalidate her no bro ain't
nobody trying to invalidate her
experience right you know you know I
think about it Gil you single too no no
no no I got a line of ladies a line yeah
like I heard you say you you got on the
on the refrigerator you got uh sex dates
oh yeah yeah with with the misses yeah
we we have we have a schedule I mean she
can't just jump she can't Mount me when
she want to we got to stay we we got to
stick to that schedule because I'm not
available every day I got a schedule too
just who's coming over which day which
week oh that's live that's laugh I like
that I like that I like that well I'm
still I'm still working on sh still
working on Uncle I'm trying to get UNCA
trying to get Uncle woman he done turn
down everybody out in offer hey oh hey
hey my schedule is anything to end with
a why Sunday Monday Tuesday Wednesday
Thursday that's the
schedule oh you woke up in the
morning CA that's what you do you ask
him early I'm a morning person right
okay now oh you remember what you
said so 2 3 o'clock in the morning when
we try to hey we tried to get it in you
said you was a born in person that's all
see they don't even I should have told
that that's all I'm asking it for yeah
it's not like I'm gonna ask you to go
walk the dog I'm just trying to
see yeah they gota you know what I'm
over there don't be doing this don't do
ain't no mosquito ain't no
mosquito hey hey oh
no he need to be on seeking Sister Wives
yeah multiple he want one to go through
all that gruesome pain n nobody can do
that five days a week three times no no
no no but I'm just no no no no I just no
no that that that ain't what I'm not
it's not every day but I'm just saying
cause just like when you ask me for
something I might not get it for you
every time but more times than not you
ask you shall
receive so when I come when I say
that's all I'm saying nobody your age
got time for all that all
right whate said hey he said he don't
dat he don't da in his age bracket
man what wrong with you I mean I told
him he needs to date women like in their
50s three or four of them right and we
gonna just rotate them it's gonna cost
you just about
250 2 250 uh I think an hour or a night
I probably throw in
here is 250 20$
25050 for the night yeah $250 for the
night that ain't bad that's a good deal
I need to get give me I need to have
some of there I got too many I got too
much overhead I got a sister I got a
brother I got a mom I got three kids a
grandkids plus I got a staff oh no man I
ain't got that kind of money well you
working over there boy yeah go down to
35 but I don't know if you want
how huh no no they they cost 35 I don't
know if you oh Oh I thought you said 35
I said okay now you in my sweet spot now
you my sweet spot n you talking no no no
they might come in there coughing you
don't want
those you
don't he what I'm
saying hey y'all y'all shut up man
just allergies I'm like hold on what you
mean allergies man ain't no allergy
ain't no allergies in January I'm I'mma
make sure I'mma make sure y'all you
gotta understand right now y'all working
y'all y'all walking in y'all purpose
right you're comfortable being alone
right now you got everything in the
world going on like Gil you comfortable
being alone even though you got you know
you got your rotation wherever you got
going on so right now y'all walking in
your purpose authentically yourselves
y'all at 80% y'all 80% you can't get no
higher than 80% right God said a man
that finded a wife find it a good thing
your other 20% to complete you as a man
is your wife and you ain't gonna never
y'all Ain gonna never have grace and
favor until you get a wife so I'm going
to find somebody for y'all that's that's
my that's my message for the day oh very
that was very touching I'm touched by
thank you I appreciate it I appreciate
it I appreciate it app I got I got y'all
though I got you I got you long as she
cost about 250 oo I'm
[Laughter]
in but in my s in in my situation oo is
that everything everything that you do
oo yeah is that you do to have options
you want to be able to situ
if I want to go I don't want to be
relegated to have a vacation where I got
to stay in the states I want to have
options if I want to go to Italy if I
want to go to Africa if I want to go to
Europe I want to be able to do that Gil
same
thing can't you you can do that I why
okay so don't try to just say hey
Shannon you got to have a 50 year old I
want
options okay I I see what you're saying
you can get a car hey you could get a
car with no op options but I want all
the bells and whistle I want a little
refrigerator in the back you know what
I'm saying yep I sure do I sure do I
want that I don't need it but I want it
you just want it okay okay I want all
the options on my when the last time you
bought a c they didn't have all the
options I bet you got all the options on
rail car I mean I I don't know what she
got on there she PA yeah you know you
bought it she paid for that no you
didn't you didy listen I'm not even the
bread winner so I'm trying to understand
why you think I even paid for it when
she the one making the money I'm just
doing don't worry about I know I know
what I pay you and I need to beo
the huh and hey and I and I know as we
as we as we starting to get go further
and further you gonna be like hey 's
what's up I'm like
huh I was like hey you got you gota you
got hey you gotta get you gotta find you
gotta bring up some more people oo you
got to find somebody else to get a
podcast so we get some
money hey hey G Gil what you said Gil I
didn't hear you you a house husband oh
yeah oh yeah yeah that's the only that's
the only reason I settle down I want
playing he yeah but it's it's different
when you find when they got some money
it's different like I I don't even know
how to act like what you mean you don't
need nothing this month you
good you give I'm getting allowance Gil
I ain't never been in no situation where
I get allowance what hey I've been
trying listen I've been trying to get
some of them uh you know they get
divorced and they take half the money I
been yeah you trying to find you one of
them I'm trying to get one of them what
yeah you know you know what would be
perfect for you Gil Miss McKenzie Jeff
Bezos
ex huh Jeff Bezos ex-wife Miss she don't
have no ass though but but she got money
that's all that matter yeah I got a I
got aers I got a little my sanders right
ass little y w pocket fat I got it okay
you know
what but that that a but that ain't
really how we that's not how we're wired
they're normally wired like that I mean
you wir like that now I think I think
that trauma that you go through because
you said that 40,000
above you see things different you see
things different now I'm I'm past that
storm right oo oo he's he's about to
come out that storm yeah you still smack
dab in
it you smack in that store so it
definitely changes your way of
thinking I think she would be perfect
for you though Gil she be perfect I mean
you're you're you're different than what
she's used to dealing with I think you
could bring a little bit excitement to
her life as opposed to what she's used
to dealing with I think I think that
that would be good I'm not sure how to
hook y'all up I mean I don't even know
how you even get in contact with someone
of of that type of status but I mean I'm
sure she might see this so good luck all
right I probably DM her she probably
don't check her DMs
[Music]